[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What score did the students of Eastside High get on the Practice Basic Skills Test in the film Lean on Me?", "correct_answer": "35%", "incorrect_answers": ["50%", "40%", "25.2%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is only a dog food brand?", "correct_answer": "Cesar", "incorrect_answers": ["Eukanuba", "Iams", "Purina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cult film was written and directed by David Lynch and had a budget of $6 million.", "correct_answer": "Blue Velvet", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry: Portrait of a Serial Killer", "Under The Cherry Moon", "Children of a Lesser God"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1973 James Bond movie has actress Jane Seymour appeared as a Bond girl?", "correct_answer": "Live and Let Die", "incorrect_answers": ["The Spy Who Loved Me", "The Man with the Golden Gun", "Diamonds Are Forever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Organic chemistry is the scientific study of the organic compounds that by definition contain which element?", "correct_answer": "Carbon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Hydrogen", "Oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The First Inauguration of a US President included saying the phrase, So help me God, and kissing the Bible after taking the oath. Who was the President that set the precedent?", "correct_answer": "George Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Jackson", "Thomas Jefferson", "James Madison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Roman emperor died of Antonine plague? This plague was actually named after him.", "correct_answer": "Marcus Aurelius", "incorrect_answers": ["Vespasian", "Claudius", "Augustus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following cannot affect the energy levels of the electrons of an atom?", "correct_answer": "All of these can affect the energy levels", "incorrect_answers": ["Absorption of energy from light (photons)", "Magnetic field", "Mechanical collision between particles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Batmans love interest in the first Batman movie?", "correct_answer": "Vicki Vale", "incorrect_answers": ["Selina Kyle", "Chase Meridian", "Barbara Gordon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which airlines  introduced  the frequent flyer program?", "correct_answer": "American Airlines", "incorrect_answers": ["KLM", "Delta Airlines", "Pan American Airlines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thanatophobia is a condition, characterized by an abnormal fear of what?", "correct_answer": "Death", "incorrect_answers": ["Needles", "Dogs", "Insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many known species of earthworm exist worldwide?", "correct_answer": "5,500", "incorrect_answers": ["3,000", "2,500", "1,000"]}]